Earth, 1980
Come!
- Slow down.
* My favorite person!
Come!
* Where are you gonna take me?
Mari.
Look.
Awesome!
I was afraid he could
not land here.
But it is rooted quickly.
And soon spread to
various places.
On the whole universe.
I do not know what
you're talking...
...but I like the
way you say it.
My heart belongs to you...
Meredith Quill.
I do not believe it, I fell
in love with an astronaut.
34 years later
Sovereign
It's time!
* Will arrive anytime anywhere.
He's a loser.
I thought you would
prefer to use a sword.
We are hired to stop the
inter-dimensional beings...
...of eating the battery, and
I want to stop by the sword?
Sword and gun is the
tool you are my tools.
But we both use guns now.
I'm just not aware of.
Drax, why do not you wear
because aero Rocket?
It's painful.
Painful?
I have sensitive nipples.
Putting me sick!
Whoops!
What about him?
What's he doing?
I set up so we could listen
to when running a mission.
Why is that important?
Blame Quill.
He is so loved by the music.
No, I agree with Drax.
* Important not directly present.
Okay.
Yes it is, Quill.
Seriously, I agree with Drax.
No, I understand.
You look quite serious now.
I can clearly see you wink.
Whoops.
I use my left eye?
I Groot.
They are not looking
at you strangely.
It was very intense.
Guardians of the Galaxy 2
Groot!
Groot, to the edge!
You could get hurt!
Good!
Do not!
Saliva back!
Fast!
Disgusting!
The skin of this creature is too thick
to be pierced from the outside.
I have to cut it from the inside.
Huh?
Do not!
Wait a minute, Drax!
Drax!
What did he do?
He said, his skin is too thick to be
pierced from the outside, so he...
That would be absurd!
- I'm trying to tell him!
The thickness of the skin is the
same from inside or outside!
I already know.
There was a wound on his neck.
Rocket, made him glance up.
Hey, sea monkeys!
On this!
Be careful, Quill!
Yes!
I am alone...
...kill these creatures!
What?
It is called what?
Battery Anulax.
Battery Harbulary.
It was not the same
as what I said.
But it is worth a
thousand units a piece.
Sovereign's why we
hired to protect him.
Be careful what you say.
They are easily offended.
Means violating the death penalty.
We thank Guards as
willing to sacrifice.
Sovereign people's lives can not
afford to take that risk. *
Every citizen who is born is
created by the community.
Perfect, both physically
and mentally.
We control the DNA of our offspring...
...they sprout in the pod birth.
I think I prefer my
men the old way.
Maybe you can give me
a history class...
...ways of our ancestors.
For academic purposes.
I will feel proud.
Yes.
On behalf of the study...
I think it's a bit...
...disgusting.
I do not like casual relationship so...
Please...
People you have something
new to our service.
Bring...
...and we will
go with pleasure.
Family meeting.
I understand that
she is your sister.
He's more valuable to me than
the hunting him in Xandar.
Our troops arrested him when he
was trying to find batteries.
Make what you like of him.
Thank you, Pastor Top Ayesha.
What breeds you, Mr. Quill?
My mother was from Earth.
And your father?
He is not from Missouri.
That's all I know.
I seemed to be in you.
Genealogy outstanding.
It looks like a hybrid...
...careless.
I heard them say, you people
are very arrogant and rude.
But that is not true immediately.
I use one eye again.
Right?
Sorry, it should be behind you.
You should feel lucky
they did not kill you.
You just tell me.
You want to buy a battery?
All right, let's bring this to Xandar
bald man and demanded his reward.
Great set of 2
The thing was about my dad.
He remembered who he was?
I know you are very
sensitive to it.
I'm not sensitive to it.
I just do not know him.
Sorry, if I look like a spree
with the Supreme Priest.
No.
I do not mind at all.
I think you care.
That's why I'm sorry.
Sorry!
Gamora not for you, Quill.
You are like a shadow.
In this universe there are
two kinds of existence.
Those who dance and
those who do not dance.
Mmm.
I found the love of
my life in war rally.
Whoops.
Everyone in the village
danced with crazy.
Unless a woman.
I Ovette.
I knew immediately he
was the one for me.
Even the world's best
melodic songs played.
He will not knock his feet.
It will not move a muscle.
Others may think he's dead.
There is a sense of immediate interest.
It would make me swell genitals.
Okay I understand.
I'm a dancer, Gamora not.
You just need to find a woman
who is pathetic, just like you.
I'm hungry.
Give me a bit of the root Yaro.
Not.
It is not yet ripe yet...
...and I hate you.
You hate me?
You left me to steal
the stone itself.
But you still standing
here, a hero.
I will be free of handcuffs
later and I'll kill you.
I swear.
Not.
You will live forever
in prison Xandar.
Hope you can.
This is weird.
We have a group of ship
Sovereign follow from behind.
Why did they do that?
Perhaps the reason Rocket
stole their batteries.
What is this!
All right.
He did not steal it.
Somehow they were chasing us.
Mystery properly.
What do you think?
It was easy to be stolen!
That's your excuse?
- Do not!
You saw the Supreme
Priest underestimate us.
I just want revenge!
I am not sure this is
your motivation altruism.
Unfortunately, the real intention of
Sovereign misunderstanding you...
...and they're trying to kill us.
- Exactly!
I'm just being sarcastic!
Whoops!
You should use a sarcastic tone!
Now I look silly!
Can we stop fighting...
...so that we survived
the war in this space?
The more ships!
- Good!
I want to kill people!
You did not kill anyone.
The ship was escorted away.
Useless!
Why postpone, Admiral?
Top clergy, the happy
battery to explode.
It can destroy the entire fleet.
The issue we are insulting
them against our people.
We hired them and
they stole from us.
It was the worst mistake.
The control module...
...shooting with intent to kill.
Planet inhabited
what is closest?
It's called Berhert.
How leap?
- Just one.
But the center is a
47-click access.
And you have to traverse
the asteroid field.
Quill, to cross...
...you got to be the
best pilot in space.
Luckily we both, I...
I am that man.
What are you doing?
I've been flying airplanes
for the past 10 years.
I specially modified to be
a pilot of a spaceship.
You specially modified
to be a fucking!
Stop.
Tonight, you will lie
down on the bed...
...and there will be flaccid
thing in your pillowcase.
And you wonder, What is this?
And it will be so because
I put shit in it.
You put shit in my bed,
I shaved your hair.
It's not bullshit me.
It belonged to Drax.
I am famous for a
large tailings.
We are about to die, and
this is what we talk about?
Seriously!
Hey, let me...
Stupid!
*
* Sovereign behind us.
Hold out.
*
Spacesuit for anxiety
or excitement
Quick, Zylak.
You can do.
Yes!
* To leap location.
*
Proceed!
Death, spaceship!
You have got to, Zylak.
Aye.
5 click!
Whoops.
They surround this field!
Some people get rid
of all of our ships!
What?
Who?
One click!
What's that?
- Who cares?
It was a leap!
Go!
He was a man.
Whoops.
He's still out there?
Groot, wear a belt!
Preparing for severe landing!
Berhert
It was amazing!
Yes!
Watch it!
Where half of our ships?
My ship.
One of you two can get
us out of this field...
...if you terbangkannya with the
brain not with your genitals!
* If in between my legs
had nothing to do...
...I'm sure I can
land this ship.
Peter.
We almost died because
of your pride.
No, because he stole...
...Anulax battery.
It's called Harbulary battery.
One, not that!
You know why I stole
the Star-Munch?
I will not be responsible
if Star-Munch.
I stole because I want to!
Why do we talk about this?
We were rescued by a man
who removed the 50 ships!
How small?
I do not know, like this?
One inch man save us?
If he's closer, I'm
sure he's bigger.
That's how our eyes work,
has raccoon fools.
Do not call me a raccoon!
Forgive me.
I've been in.
I mean panda waste.
It is better?
I do not know.
It is more severe, very severe.
You are...
Hey!
I can not take it with you!
- Do not! Go!
Some people follow you
through the leap.
Let me go.
You need my help.
I'm not stupid, Nebula.
You foolish to refuse
to assist in the match.
You will attack when it is released.
I will not do so.
You think the thugs will
learn how to lie well.
I'm sure it's a human
one inch of it.
After a long time,
finally to see you.
And who are you?
I remember, my face was so
handsome enough to explain.
My name is Ego...
...and I'm the father, Peter.
Contraxia
You know what they say...
You're out of luck
until you get it back.
Yondu!
Download here!
After years with no results...
...I ended up marrying this woman.
I said, Aleta, I love you...
...but you've lost your mind!
What's more, he did so.
I can not trust him.
Stake.
It's been a long time.
Apparently, the place is
somewhat less suggestive.
Stake.
There are 100 groups Ravager, Sneeper.
You lost 99 trade you because
you are dealing with.
Please, sir.
Help!
Stay away from me.
You go die!
I do not care what
you think about me!
So, why did you come with us?
For you will hear what I said!
I do not need to hear anything!
You break the rules!
Ravager got a raw
deal with the boy!
I told you!
I do not know what's going on!
You do not know because you do not want
to know, because it makes you rich.
I insisted on a place at the table.
I use this fire, like you.
You may dress like us...
...but you will not hear Hon
freedom when you die, Yondu.
And Varna Orgord...
...will not be hoisted on your grave.
If you recall...
I like to throw you...
...you are wrong.
You disappoint us all.
Pathetic.
First, Quill betrays us...
...and Yondu let him alone.
We follow him...
...because he's not afraid to
make what should have been made.
Apparently, he was gentle.
If he had been lenient
why are you whispering?
You know I'm right, Kraglin.
You better be careful when
talking about our captain.
Who is that?
Yondu Udonta.
I have a suggestion for you.
I hired Yondu to take you...
...after your mother died.
But, on the return you...
...Yondu take care of you.
I do not know why.
I'll tell you why.
My skinny boy who can squeeze
into places adults *
It is easier to steal *
Since then I began to
keep track of you. *
I remember Yondu is your father.
What?
We've been together.
You remember Yondu my real dad?
You two look alike.
He's blue!
No, he's not my father!
Yondu is the person
who kidnapped me.
At the worst, so I
learned to fight.
Fun scare me by
threatening to eat me.
Eat you?
- Yes.
It was a mess!
How did you track us?
In the place I live in, on the
outskirts of the mystery...
...we hear about people
called Star-Lord.
Why do not we go there now?
Your friend invited.
Including monkey-faced triangles.
I promise to you...
...it's not like a
place you've ever seen.
And there...
I can tell you a
special history.
Finally can be...
...the father of my dreams.
Forgive me.
I have to go pee.
I do not believe.
Let's take a break.
I Mantis.
What are you doing?
Smile.
I heard, it acts to
make others like you.
No, if you are creating.
I grew up alone on
the planet Ego.
I do not understand the
complexities of social interaction.
May I touch your dog?
It's very cute.
Can.
This is called playing with people!
I like!
I made an excuse!
Please help!
After all this time, you
show up and suddenly...
...you want to be my father?
- I understand.
And also, this may be a trap.
Kree real, Ravager...
...they want to kill us.
- One idea, but...
But, what?
What story did you tell
me about Zard Hasselfrau?
Who?
He has a miracle boat.
David Hasselhoff?
Really.
Not a miracle boat.
A car talk.
Why did he speak?
To help him fight the criminals,
and become supporters.
Childhood, you take a picture
of him in your pocket...
and you will tell all
the other children...
...he is your father,
but he is out of town.
Recording Knight Rider
or create a group show in Germany.
I tell when drunk.
Why do you say that now?
I love that story.
I hate that story.
It's so sad!
Childhood, I always saw other
kids playing with their father.
And I just wanted so, over
all things in the world.
That's what I mean, Peter.
What if this person
is you Hasselhoff?
If he actually mean...
...we kill him any time.
You left me with the weasel?
He's not a fox.
Shoot him if he was suspicious.
Or like hearts.
Just a couple of days.
We will be back here before the
Rockets finished repairing the ship.
What if Sovereign come?
Odds are they know where we are.
Let's go.
I worry if we split up.
Oh, you're like an old man.
Because I'm smart?
Why do you have so many bags?
I do not want Groot
play my stuff.
I hope your father is not
as bad as you, the orphans.
What is your goal?
Make everyone hate you?
Because it is successful.
Can I ask you a
personal question?
Nobody ever asked me
a personal question.
Antena you, it's what?
Usefulness?
Yes, I have a bet and Quill.
You should not mention about it.
I said...
and at the door if
you're too low...
...the antenna you will feel it and
prevent you from a decapitated head.
Really.
And if it other than...
...you beheaded by
a low door, I win.
It is not to feel the
height of the door.
I feel...
...it has to do with
my telepathic ability.
What's that?
If I touch someone, I can
feel their feelings.
You read the thoughts of others?
- Not.
People can know the mind telepathy.
Feelings of empathy.
Emotions.
Can I touch it?
Can.
You love.
I think I have feelings
of love for everyone.
Not.
Romantic, sexual love.
Do not have.
For him!
- Not.
It was not.
Okay.
He had to tell everyone
you hidden secrets.
Hey, I think you're already in.
You should be ashamed!
Touch me!
I've never felt like
this feeling amused.
It's not fair.
Quill.
If you touch me, you
will feel a broken jaw.
I can also change a
person's feelings.
Like what?
If I touch people sad...
...I can warm his
heart for a moment.
I can make a good person bad.
But I used to use it to
help my master bedroom.
He always lie at night
thinking about her.
Try to do to me.
Sleep.
I love this song.
There!
Not so strong again
without your game.
Right?
Move!
Whoops.
Hey, rats!
Hello there, blue
people are stupid?
Not bad.
Apparently, we have a
very good point here.
The golden girl high
opinion of himself...
has offered a lot of money for
you and your friends drag him...
...because he wants
to kill you all.
Your Friend...
They are too many.
He needs my help.
If you're worried about him...
...you have to let
me out of this bind.
They will kill him!
Actually, I was
happy to find you.
I put the sensors
on your boat...
...during the war with Xandar.
Promise me you will
not hurt Groot...
...and I'll tell you
where the battery was.
You good luck, my
words do not count.
If not, I have to drag you.
If so, what are you gonna do?
We will take the battery.
It's worth what?
Quarter of a million on the open market.
Highest Priest was
offering us a million.
Quarter only 1/3 of it!
Not third quarter.
Quarter is 25.
Not.
We can not buy a pair
of shoes with 25 units.
Enough!
Whatever, we're not so stupid to help
kill the Guardians of the Galaxy!
The entire Nova Corps will hunt us.
That is not true!
My son spoke this time, captain.
No matter how many times
Quill betray you...
...you protect him like
we all got very important.
I support you!
Calm, Kraglin.
That's right, man.
He was lenient.
It feels, it's time
to change the head.
Put down your weapons!
Whoa!
There must be a good
solution for this situation.
Or a violent way in which
I was standing there.
Hey, all.
It is not yet ripe!
Planet Ego
Welcome, all, to my world.
You have your own planet?
Come on.
Lebuh similar to the Earth.
Very humble.
I like.
I was also very touched.
You have a planet and can destroy
the spacecraft without spacesuits.
What are you actually?
I called the Celestial.
Celestial, like God?
T a little.
At least, there are days I
feel like Drax generous.
I am not sure where I came from.
The first thing I remember *
*
More than millions of years...
...I learned to control
molecules around me.
I became more clever and strong.
And I continue to
build from there.
Layer upon layer...
planet are you running now...
Whoa...
But I want more.
I want...
...meaning.
There must be a life out
there in the universe...
...other than myself , perhaps.
So, I decided to look it up.
I create...
biological life as I imagine...
...up to the smallest detail.
You have created a penis?
Hey!
What's the problem with you?
If he is a planet, how did he
get the kid with your mother?
He will destroy your mother!
I do not need to hear
how my parents...
Why?
My father's story of how he made my
mother pregnant, each winter solstice.
It was indecent.
It is very beautiful.
You Earth people have emotional problems.
Yes, Drax.
I have a penis.
Thank you.
It's not as bad as you think.
I also have a sense of pain
and digestive system...
...and all the things there.
I want to feel what it
feels to be a human being.
As I explore in the stars...
until I found...
...what I want.
Life.
I am not alone in this universe.
When you met my mother?
Shortly afterwards.
With Meredith, the first
time I feel love.
I call him my lily river.
And for the love of it, Peter...
You.
I've been looking for you.
And when I heard about
a man on the Earth...
who hold the stone in his hand
Infiniti without dying...
...I know you must be the
son of the woman I love.
If you love her, why
did you leave him?
This rebellion!
You bastard!
Captain!
Help me!
Please help!
Captain!
It is you who kill people...
...to lead them
down the wrong path.
For you weak.
And stupid!
It's time to Ravenger...
to come back to the glory
days of the new captain...
Taserface!
Sorry.
Your name is...
Is Taserface?
Really.
Are you shoot a
taser on your face?
It's a metaphor!
Yes!
For what?
Because it's a scary name...
...on those who hear it.
Okay.
Okay...
What you said...
You shut up.
You next.
Udonta, I've been
waiting to do...
What?
Forgive me.
I kept imagining
when you wake up...
look in the mirror intently
and said to myself...
You know what the name of a
very scary person? Taserface!
That's what I hear
you in my brain.
What is the name of the second one are you?
Schrotus Hat?
The new plan.
We'll kill you first.
Better dead than
live a lifetime...
...as a useless person who remembers
the name Taserface is fashionable.
Enough for today's murder.
He is the son of Thanos.
I thought you were the worst
torturers in the universe.
That's when my father was
still paying my bills.
Top clergy wanted to
kill the fox itself.
And his head is a reward in
about 12 provinces Kree.
I guarantee...
It is not easy to wear me like a
parent without a magic wand...
...or wild forest speak.
I want to reward the 10% of...
...and some other things.
We have a lot of hand...
...if that does not work.
- It's fine.
You remember Kree captain
would kill them?
People let their singer Kree *
but he got sick.
This is it.
Boat best that we have.
Cities Ego planet
in the system *
We'll send you 10%
after we *
What would you do
with the money?
Ketch time, my father always told me
and Gamora fighting during training.
Whenever my sister won...
...my father will be replaced
with something on my machine.
He said he wanted me
to be comparable.
But he won...
many times and never avoid *
So, after I kill my sister...
...I'm going to buy a warship with
every weapon that carries death.
I would rush to my father like a
dog and I'll tear him slowly...
one by one...
until he felt a bit of pain
agonizing endlessly...
...as I feel each day.
Yes.
I am talking about
a beautiful chain.
Or a pretty hat.
Something that makes the
girl said, It's beautiful.
Anyway, congratulations
to explore.
My mother told my father
of all the stars.
He was suffering from brain cancer.
So, everyone thought he was delusional.
Peter...
I really want to believe
it all, really.
But you leave...
The best woman...
...to die alone.
I do not mean to leave
your mother, Peter.
If I rarely go back
to my planet...
and light in it...
...This form will wither and disappear.
Why do not you go back?
Why are you sending Yondu?
A robber, who came
to take me away.
I love you, Peter!
I'm not willing to
go down to Earth...
...see she's gone!
You can not imagine the feeling!
I know how you feel it!
I had to see him die!
In my life that
millions of years...
...I made a lot of mistakes, Peter.
But you're not one of them.
Please give me a chance to
be the father he wants.
There are many things I have to
teach you about on this planet...
...and the light in it.
It's a part of you, Peter.
What do you mean?
Give me your hand, my son.
Here.
Hold this.
Now, close your eyes
and concentrate.
Bring your brain to the
heart of the planet.
Yes!
Wow!
It's fine.
Calm down.
Pay attention.
You can do.
Try again.
Yes!
Yes, now bentukkannya.
Feel that energy.
So.
You're back.
Peter.
How do you get to the
planet's stupid and weird?
Ego see me when I was
in the form of larvae.
Orphans in my world.
He exaggerated my own and
be a companion at his side.
So, you are a pet.
Presumably.
Usually, people
want cute animals.
Why the ego wants an ugly beast?
I'm ugly?
You can scare people
when they see fit.
But it was good also.
When you're ugly and
nobody loves you...
...you know they
love you sincerely.
Beautiful people do not
know who to believe.
If so, I am very
proud to be ugly.
The pool reminded
me of a time...
...when I take my son to the
lake is forgotten in my world.
He's just like you.
Disgusting?
Innocent.
Drax?
There's something I
need to tell you.
Why is this?
The lady beetle
is my new friend.
I learned a lot of things,
like my pets and ugly.
You got ugly.
Drax!
What are you talking about?
Mantis.
Can you show us where you live?
Why no other creature
on the planet?
This planet is Ego.
A dog will not pick lice
to live on her body.
And ye are not lice?
I tick that no purpose.
I help him sleep.
What do you want to tell
Drax before I came in?
Do not have.
Where you live here.
We will send you into
Kree tomorrow morning.
You two can not hold
much longer after this.
Okay, Taserface.
Tell the others, we say...
Hi, Taserface!
How about this little tree?
I can crushed with stones?
Do not, Gef.
He's too cute to kill.
Take him to a tailor.
Do not get me wrong, but
you're so useless employees.
I'm a slave for 20 years
until my release Stake.
He gave me a place in Ravager.
He said, I just have
to follow any rules.
But I was young...
...greedy and stupid.
As you steal the battery.
It all Drax.
I, stake and the other captain...
We have no difference as
you and your friends.
The only family I have.
When I broke that rule...
...they threw me.
Indeed, I should receive.
Quiet, drama queen.
You probably deserve
it, but I do not.
We should get out of here.
Where Quill?
He came out with his father.
Ego?
- Yes.
Today is full of stupid name.
For a moment, I feel good.
But it was spoiled
by the ugly teeth.
As a professional, or what?
*
Why do not you send Quill
to Ego as promised?
He was emaciated.
To insert a place that we can not afford.
Good to steal.
I know how to get out of here.
We need the help of
your little friends.
Mascot!
The little boy was angry!
He needed a drink!
Look how cute he is
when he's angry.
He's very cute.
Hey, stick!
Come here.
Mari.
What is this.
What did they do to him?
Hey, you want to
help us out of here?
I want you to take
something for me.
In the captain's room, there
is one flipper prototype.
The thing that I
have in the head.
There is a drawer by the bed.
It's in there. Red.
You understand?
It was in my pants.
I'm sure she does not
understand what you say.
You need to explain
more clearly.
It flipper prototype.
It orloni.
It had fins, Groot.
Let me tell you this time.
All right.
It points Vorker.
He was out while he slept.
Go, look again.
But it points to stay here.
Why?
She'll wake up tomorrow...
and he would not know...
...where his eyes!
That table.
We say, it is this.
Tell me, do you have
a fridge in here...
...a few stubbed toes.
Okay, we agree we will not
talk about this anymore.
Drawers that you have to go
there this symbol on it.
Okay?
What? Not!
He remembered, you tell
him to wear it as a hat.
That's not what I said!
I Groot!
- He was relieved because you do not ask her to wear.
I Groot.
- In hate hats.
In all people, not himself.
I Groot.
Instant seem strange rattle...
...after that you noticed
some new head is a hat.
That's why you do not like the hat?
It was an important
discussion today?
Not that.
I do not mean to be disloyal.
They killed all my friends.
Set to be released
third quadrant.
One more.
Do you have any copies of
music Quill on this ship?
He's been taken!
Yondu fins take it!
Go!
Down there!
You're crazy.
The whole ship will explode.
Not all of them.
Who is this?
I'll send the coordinates
to ship Yondu.
Remove the quadrant!
- Good, Captain!
I only have one request.
Priests Meet Top ye...
...tell him the names of
people who will put her fate.
Taserface!
Where, captain?
Ego.
Do not!
Not bad for the body of mammals
jump more than 50 times at a time.
I know.
We will make a 700!
So, I think all this might
belong to me later.
Rocket, you hear?
What are you doing, Peter?
Dance with me.
I'm not going to dance with you.
The Sam Cooke...
...one of the best
singers on Earth.
Drax guess you're not a dancer.
If you tell anyone about this...
...I'll kill you.
If we are going to do something
that can not be called among us?
What is it that can not be called?
That is...
Cheer , Sam and Diane...
a man and woman in the
TV show who love...
...but not admitted because if
admitted, the audience will be reduced.
Something like that.
There are no objects that
can not be mentioned.
So, this is a dilemma, because if you
call, it will continue to call...
...and you'll be a liar.
So, with no call...
...you're speaking the truth
and agree with something.
No, that's not what I...
What we should discuss
now is about this place.
Feels like something wrong.
What are you talking about?
You told me to come here.
The woman, Mantis...
...he was afraid of something.
You want to take it from me?
Not.
He's my father.
He was my ancestor.
You have descended on Earth and
you do not want to go back there.
Again, you told me to come.
And the Earth is where my
mother died in front of me.
Not because the place where it
exists and is here like a shadow.
This place exists!
I'm half human, remember?
Half that's what I worry about.
I understand.
You jealous...
...because I'm half god and
you love it when I am weak.
From the start you're so arrogant.
I can not get a Rocket!
I'm going out to
get a clear line.
You know what?
This is not Cheer !
This is the case where
people are willing to...
receive new possibilities,
and the other was a bully...
...who do not believe in anyone!
Things that would not exist! *
Therefore it will be 0 ratings.
I do not know, what it Cheer ?
Eventually I found my family.
You understand me?
I thought you had
forgotten the family.
Crazy person!
Let me correct you!
I win.
I won the tournament.
Not.
I save your life.
You are a fool let me live.
You let me live!
I do not need you to beat me!
I do not fly across the
universe just to win.
Do not tell me what I wanted.
I do not ever tell
me what you want!
That's obvious!
You just want to win.
And I just want a sister!
You're all I have.
But you have to want to win.
Thanos pull my eyes
out of your head...
and my brain out of the skull...
and my hands on the body...
...as a result of you.
Great set of 2
You got any?
I saw your girlfriend
rushed out earlier.
Yes.
Sure enough...
...You hear this song as well.
You know...
- Brandy?
By the Looking Glass?
Your mother's favorite song.
That is correct.
One of the best musical
composition on Earth.
Perhaps the best of the best.
Yes!
Peter, we like a
gob in the song.
As a child my mother
embodied in...
...or the freedom
you give the Gamora.
Ocean recall his browser.
He love the girl, but
it was not his place.
Ocean summon him as a great
man in history to call on.
And sometimes we are denied
the pleasure of men.
You may not be a man, but I do.
No, Peter.
Death is like a
stranger in our...
...while the light was still
burning in the planet.
I'm immortal?
Really?
Yes!
As long as this light still exists.
And I can use light to
create an amazing thing...
...like how do you build this planet?
It may need a few million
years of training...
...before you become proficient.
But, yes!
What?
It's like building a 800-foot
statue of Pac-Man and Skeletor...
...and Heather Locklear.
You can do anything you want.
I will do something quite strange.
You know, Peter.
It's a big responsibility.
Only we can recreate
this natural...
Only we can stop the universe...
...and move it to
where you should go.
How?
Follow me.
Drax.
Drax!
I have something to say.
Sorry.
But I like a woman with
a more moderate body.
What?
I'm trying to push you to
tell that you're so ugly.
Not.
It was not my intention.
What are you doing?
I would like to imagine
us together physically.
Drax.
I do not like you so.
I also did not like
that kind of like you.
Hey!
Needless to result.
Listen!
Ego can have what he wants.
I should have told you sooner.
I was stupid.
You're in danger.
What's that?
Now, you have to adjust yourself
to the way you understand life.
All objects around us,
including the girl...
Everything is temporary.
It is we who remain timeless.
Did not live forever
would be bored?
Unless you have a goal, Peter.
That's why you're here.
I've told you so many before.
I have never ceased
to push to find life.
But I got to tell you
how I finally found it.
Everything is...
...disappointing.
From there I received...
...deep awareness.
My natural desire to
find another life...
...but not to live with them.
Peter.
I have found the meaning.
I see.
Immortality!
No.
We need to get out of this planet.
Ouch.
Before I interrupted savagely...
At that time, I was
a Federal Express.
What are you doing, boy?
I heard you talk about him...
...that the Ego is bad news.
We are here to save Quill.
For what?
To honor? To love?
Not.
I do not care about that feeling.
I want to save Quill
to prove me better!
I can be better than him.
You laugh at me for what?
You can trick yourself and
others, but you can not fool me.
I know who you really are.
You do not know anything
about me, weak.
I know everything about you.
I know you behave
brutal and gritty...
...but actually you
are most afraid of.
Shut up!
I know you stole a battery
that you do not need...
and you force people who are
willing to tolerate you...
Because little love...
...remind you of just how big and
empty your hearts to the truth.
I said, shut up!
I know a scientist who you love but
do not care about you directly.
I'm serious!
As my parents sold me...
...children of their own, to make slaves.
I know you are, boy.
For you are like me.
What kind of partner we have?
Type that would go against
a planet, I think.
All right!
Instant.
Fighting what?
Who are you really?
What is this place?
Gamora, let her go!
The body of the
cave, who are they?
You're afraid.
I call it, the extension.
It is my goal.
Now, it is your goal as well.
It's beautiful.
For thousands of years...
I planted a huge extension of me...
...in the thousands worldwide.
I have to fulfill the main
goal of a real life...
To grow and spread...
includes everything that exists...
so everything is...
...me.
What did he do to me?
He has told me everything.
I only have one problem.
A Space Creature does not have
sufficient authority for this program.
But two Space Creatures...
...may be able to achieve now.
The body was...
...is his son.
Of all my work...
most require trick is...
...I attempted grafting
of DNA with other species.
I hope that the relationship
should be pretty random...
...for the extension of my altered.
I told Yondu send people to me.
It's against the rules, but I
Ravager pay compensation to many...
...and to comfort her, I
said, I will not hurt them.
I mean, it was right.
They will not feel anything.
But all disappoint me.
No person who has a
gene Creatures Space.
But you have, Peter.
Of all my seed...
...only you who is no
relation to the light.
We need to find Peter now
and get out of this planet.
Ego must be affecting him now.
Then, we go.
- Not!
He's our friend.
- You all just...
...screaming to each other.
You're not his friend.
That's right.
We are one family.
We will not leave anyone.
Maybe except you.
Ouch.
For the first time in my life...
...I'm not alone!
Why?
My friend.
Listen.
It's human nature for you, Peter.
Yes.
We are more of everything.
Now...
- But my mother...
You say you love her.
That's right.
Lotus river I know all the lyrics
to every song played on the radio.
I went back to Earth to
see him in three times.
And I knew if I went
back the 4th time...
...I will not go.
Extension of this...
...is the main reason for my
existence will be exhausted.
So, I did what I should do.
But rather reluctantly me to put
it on the head of her tumor.
What?
I know...
...it sounds less fun.
We remember, who are you?
You killed my mother!
I have tried...
all efforts...
to find a form of...
the most suitable for you...
...and this is how you thank?
You have minded adults.
I wanna do it together...
*... that you're supposed
to be used as a battery.
Finally!
Rocket.
Place the transmitter near
it with so I can find you. *
We were in the old building
Yondu tool used...
...to divide two A'askavaria Bank.
Ego was crazy.
I know.
Ready.
Cut him loose, Kraglin.
No.
Peter.
This is the ocean.
*
What happened?
Bank, Groot! *
I told you there was
something wrong. *
I also think so.
So, *
I *
*
There are no objects
that can not talk.
What are you doing?
You can kill us all.
Thank you, Rocket?
They are in control.
Not.
This is just an extension of...
...looks and real.
He'll be back shortly.
What is Smurfette doing here?
What I do is to go to
a place of safety.
He's trying to kill me!
I saved you, stupid weasel!
He's not a fox.
I Groot.
- I'm not a raccoon as well.
Raccoon .
Whatever.
How do we want to kill *
There is one main core. *
His mind, his soul, whatever,
have a framework of protection.
It's in the cave...
...under the surface.
Yondu?
Rocket engines are dead.
I think I should be
proud of my thin boy.
If not, you're sending
me to this madman.
You remember?
That's why I saved you, you idiot.
That's what you
said to me, silly.
Once I know what happened
to the other children...
...I will send you to him.
You said, you're
going to eat me.
It was just a mess.
Not for me!
You both did a lot of problems.
Of course, I have a problem.
That's my dad's scary!
*
We should go up!
- Can not.
The ego wants to rid the
universe as we know it.
We have to kill him.
Rocket!
Good!
So, we save the universe again?
It tastes.
Great!
We can not raise our
prices again...
...if we are to be the
savior of the universe twice.
I really do not believe
that's what you think.
It was just a random thought.
I remember, we were friends.
Of course, I worry about
the planet and building...
...and all the animals in the planet.
And all the people.
Meh.
Grumpy puppy is very cute.
He made me almost want to die!
Pilots...
...drop the unit representative.
Our detectors detect the battery
under the planet's surface.
Jump!
Captain?
Tell me, why does the
ego wants you here?
He needs to connect my
genetics at the light...
...to destroy the universe.
He tried to teach me how
to control his powers.
So, can you?
A little bit.
I make a ball.
A ball?
I've thought all my efforts.
That's all I can do.
You think ?
You think, when I created
this arrow fly...
...I use my head?
Wow.
There.
That is the main thrust of the Ego.
Ore was thick, Rocket.
I solved it.
We need to fast.
It will not take long
to find our Ego.
Steady bit.
We dig into the
center, we kill him!
Captain?
What he, Kraglin?
Hey, remember the girl Ayesha?
Yes why?
Why do not you use
the laser gun?
He blew up our generator.
I think I made a small
explosive device.
Explosive device did not
work without a power source.
Well, we have this.
Is it enough to kill the ego?
If successful, it will
create a chain reaction...
...to the whole nervous system.
What does that mean?
The whole planet is going to explode.
We need to get out
of here quickly.
I have made a timer.
Go!
He came.
Did not you say you
can make her fall?
While she wants.
He's too strong.
I can not afford!
You do not have to
believe in yourself...
...because I believe in you.
Up!
I do not think he can do it...
...with weak and
skinny like that.
I do not know how
long I can last.
Iron is too thick...
...the bomb was memorable.
We need to put it on
the main terrace Ego.
And we all can not *
into a small hole.
So...
It was a bad idea.
That's the only idea we have.
Indeed disbelief.
Rockets do this.
Rockets do it.
That was my day.
Well, first you flick the
switch, and this switch.
*
Then you press this button.
It will give you 5 minutes
to get out of there.
Now, whatever you do...
...do not press this button.
For this bomb will explode
immediately and we will all die.
Now, repeat back what I said.
I Groot.
- Yes.
- That's right.
I Groot.
- Not!
No, it's a button that
will kill everyone!
One more time.
I Groot.
- Yes.
- That's right.
I Groot.
- Not!
*
Button which you should press?
Show.
Not!
Hey, you make him afraid!
Shut up!
Give me the tape!
Those who have the tape?
I would like to
attach to the death.
I have no tape.
Let me check.
Hey, Yondu...
You have the tape?
Gamora?
Tape!
Nevermind.
Drax?
You have the tape?
Yes, Scotch tape shall be well.
*
Nobody band!
A tape did not exist?
Yes.
You ask the Nebula?
Yes!
Are you sure?
I asked Yondu...
...and he sat down next to him.
I know you're lying!
There are priceless battery and
the atomic bomb in your bag.
If those who have the
tape, it is you!
That's my point!
I have to do everything!
You are wasting time here!
We will all die.
Rocket engines off again!
We are finished
without a generator!
Guardian...
Maybe he can give
you peace of...
...that your death
was not in vain.
It will serve as a warning...
...to those who
want to betray us.
Do not fooling Sovereign.
It would be a pain.
Promise is promise.
Not!
We are going to explode!
Peter!
Not!
What?
You look like Mary Poppins.
He chic?
Yes, he is stylish.
All I'm asking for Mary Poppins!
Hey!
He just fainted.
How long before the
bombs explode?
If a situation where Groot
did not kill us all...
...about 6 minutes.
Kraglin, we need to
postpone the quadrant.
Time to leave in 5 minutes.
Well, captain.
A person should be above the
current Kraglin arrived.
Drax, bring Mantis.
My Nipples!
Gamora!
Peter!
Forget it.
Come on, Peter.
I know this is not what you want.
I'm not the kind of dad let
you make a choice like that.
Yes!
Soon, Peter, but
we just got here.
So, do not make me angry!
*
Go!
I already told you...
...I do not want
to do it alone.
You can not deny...
...the purpose of the universe
that have been bestowed on you.
Listen, I want you all to go.
What is this?
He did not have to happen like this, Peter.
Why are you destroying
our chances?
Do not pretend to yourself.
One in a billion.
Trillion, even more.
What greater purpose
this life can give?
I did not use my head
for flying arrows!
I use my heart...
You should not have killed my
mother and my Walkman destroyed.
Groot, if you can
hear me, hurry!
I do not know how much longer
Quill can distract him!
Groot, quickly!
Yondu, we are about to explode!
Go to the ship!
I do not go without Quill!
You need to take care of the timber!
I'm not going without you!
My whole life, I've never
done the right thing.
You have to give it.
An aero spacesuits and tools.
I have each of them.
I Groot!
What's that?
He says, Welcome to the
Guardians of the Galaxy.
Just do not call him rude verse.
Goodbye, wood.
We need to talk more
about your language.
Where is Peter?
Rocket, where is he?
Rocket?
Look at me!
Where is she?
No, I will not
leave without her.
Sorry.
I can only just lost
a friend today.
Kraglin, go!
Wait.
Quill will return?
Rocket, where Quill?
Rocket!
Where Quill?
Do we have to stop it.
Stop.
Listen!
You are a god.
If you kill me...
...you will be like a normal person.
So, what's the problem?
Do not!
He may be your father,
but he's not your dad.
Sorry, I have not
done the right thing.
I am very fortunate to be
able to call you my son.
What?
Yondu, what did you do this?
Do not.
Yondu!
Do not!
I told Gamora...
...when I was little, I consider
as my father David Hasselhoff.
He is a singer and actor from *
famous.
Earlier, I noticed...
Yondu no cars to speak but
he has a flying arrow.
She was not a beautiful
voice like an angel...
...but he's got a whistle.
Yondu and David Hasselhoff have
an interesting adventure...
and get acquainted with a beautiful woman...
...and fighting robots.
I think, in the end David
Hasselhoff it has become my father.
Only you alone, Yondu.
I do have a great dad.
What I want to say here is...
sometimes the things you want to
look for the rest of your life...
...are with you during this time.
You just do not realize.
I Groot.
He was there to call you wood.
Nebula.
I'm also a boy like you.
Every day, I worried about
how to survive the next day.
And I never cared what
Thanos had made with you.
I tried to correct the situation.
There is a little boy just like you...
...in the entire
universe is in danger.
You can be with
us and help them.
I will help them if they
want to kill Thanos.
I did not know it
could be achieved.
You will always be my brother.
Pete!
The captain found
something in store waste.
Said, you will return
to our society someday.
What is this?
It's called Zune.
Everyone heard this thing
on Earth right now.
It contained 300 songs in it.
300 songs?
Wait.
Rocket take all the
pieces and re-fix.
I think Yondu want
you to have it.
Thank you.
Capt.
Father and Son Cat Stevens
They're coming.
What?
I told the guys in Ravager
Yondu what he did.
It was a funeral
entourage Ravager.
Yes!
He did not disappoint
us this time, captain.
She never disappoint.
Never.
Goodbye, old friend.
Yondu Udonta, I will see
you again at the stars.
*
Not.
Must be.
What?
Just...
There is something unspeakable.
It's beautiful.
Really.
Just like you.
Just inside.
Guardians of the Galaxy will return
You know, it's a shame...
...need a tragedy to lose Yondu
to bring us all together again.
But I think he'd be proud
if we come back as a team.
I agree.
Me too.
I really miss you all!
Really.
Why do not we go
steal something?
Top clergy, the
council is waiting.
They are very worried me
wasting their resources.
*
...their anger will disappear.
It was my son.
*
More powerful, more beautiful...
...more capable, to destroy
the Galactic Guardians.
I think I should call her.
Adam.